http://www.realtimeuk.com/cookie-policy-uk/

This Cookie Policy was last updated on 5th October 2020 and applies to citizens of the United Kingdom.1. IntroductionOur website, https://www.realtimeuk.com (hereinafter: "the website") uses cookies and other related technologies (for convenience all technologies are referred to as "cookies"). Cookies are also placed by third parties we have engaged. In the document below we inform you about the use of cookies on our website.2. What are cookies?A cookie is a small simple file that is sent along with pages of this website and stored by your browser on the hard drive of your computer or another device. The information stored therein may be returned to our servers or to the servers of the relevant third parties during a subsequent visit.3. What are scripts?A script is a piece of programme code that is used to make our website function properly and interactively. This code is executed on our server or on your device.4. What is a web beacon?A web beacon (or a pixel tag) is a small, invisible piece of text or image on a website that is used to monitor traffic on a website. In order to do this, various data about you is stored using web beacons.5. Cookies5.1 Technical or functional cookiesSome cookies ensure that certain parts of the website work properly and that your user preferences remain known. By placing functional cookies, we make it easier for you to visit our website. This way, you do not need to repeatedly enter the same information when visiting our website and, for example, the items remain in your shopping cart until you have paid. We may place these cookies without your consent.5.2 Analytical cookiesWe use analytical cookies to optimize the website experience for our users. With these analytical cookies we get insights in the usage of our website. We ask your permission to place analytical cookies.5.3 Marketing/Tracking cookiesMarketing/Tracking cookies are cookies or any other form of local storage, used to create user profiles to display advertising or to track the user on this website or across several websites for similar marketing purposes.5.4 Social media buttonsOn our website we have included buttons for Facebook, Twitter, LinkedIn, Instagram and Pinterest to promote webpages (e.g. “like”, “pin”) or share (e.g. “tweet”) on social networks like Facebook, Twitter, LinkedIn, Instagram and Pinterest. These buttons work using pieces of code coming from Facebook, Twitter, LinkedIn, Instagram and Pinterest themselves. This code places cookies. These social media buttons also can store and process certain information, so a personalized advertisement can be shown to you.Please read the privacy statement of these social networks (which can change regularly) to read what they do with your (personal) data which they process using these cookies. The data that is retrieved is anonymized as much as possible. Facebook, Twitter, LinkedIn, Instagram and Pinterest are located in the United States.6. Placed cookiesHotjar
Usage
We use Hotjar for heat maps and screen recordings.
Sharing data
For more information, please read the Hotjar Privacy Statement.
Statistics
Name
_hjid
Retention
1 year
Function
Store a unique user ID
Statistics (anonymous)
Name
_hjIncludedInSample
Retention
session
Function
Store anonymized statistics
Google Analytics
Usage
We use Google Analytics for website statistics.
Sharing data
For more information, please read the Google Analytics Privacy Statement.
Statistics (anonymous)
Name
_ga
Retention
2 years
Function
Name
_gid
Retention
Usage
We use Complianz for cookie consent management.
Sharing data
For more information, please read the Complianz Privacy Statement.
Functional
Name
cmplz_all
Retention
365 days
Function
Store cookie consent preferences
Name
Usage
We use Facebook for display of recent social posts and/or social share buttons.
Sharing data
For more information, please read the Facebook Privacy Statement.
Marketing/Tracking
Name
_fbc
Retention
2 years
Function
Stores last visit
Name
Usage
We use Google Fonts for display of webfonts.
Sharing data
For more information, please read the Google Fonts Privacy Statement.
Marketing/Tracking
Name
Google Fonts API
Retention
none
Function
Request user IP address
Google Maps
Usage
We use Google Maps for maps display.
Sharing data
For more information, please read the Google Maps Privacy Statement.
Marketing/Tracking
Name
Google Maps API
Retention
none
Function
Request user IP address
Vimeo
Usage
We use Vimeo for video display.
Sharing data
For more information, please read the Vimeo Privacy Statement.
Statistics
Name
__utmt_player
Retention
10 minutes
Function
Track audience reach
Name
Usage
We use YouTube for video display.
Sharing data
For more information, please read the YouTube Privacy Statement.
Marketing/Tracking
Name
GPS
Retention
session
Function
Store location data
Functional
Usage
We use LinkedIn for display of recent social posts and/or social share buttons.
Sharing data
For more information, please read the LinkedIn Privacy Statement.
Marketing/Tracking
Name
bcookie
Retention
2 years
Function
Store browser details
Name
Usage
We use Twitter for display of recent social posts and/or social share buttons.
Sharing data
For more information, please read the Twitter Privacy Statement.
Functional
Name
local_storage_support_test
Retention
persistent
Function
Load balancing functionality
Marketing/Tracking
Function
7. ConsentWhen you visit our website for the first time, we will show you a pop-up with an explanation about cookies. As soon as you click on "Save preferences", you consent to us using the categories of cookies and plug-ins you selected in the pop-up, as described in this Cookie Policy. You can disable the use of cookies via your browser, but please note that our website may no longer work properly.7.1 Manage your consent settings8. Your rights with respect to personal dataYou have the following rights with respect to your personal data:
You have the right to know why your personal data is needed, what will happen to it, and how long it will be retained for.
Right of access: You have the right to access your personal data that is known to us.
Right to rectification: you have the right to supplement, correct, have deleted or blocked your personal data whenever you wish.
If you give us your consent to process your data, you have the right to revoke that consent and to have your personal data deleted.
Right to transfer your data: you have the right to request all your personal data from the controller and transfer it in its entirety to another controller.
Right to object: you may object to the processing of your data. We comply with this, unless there are justified grounds for processing.
To exercise these rights, please contact us. Please refer to the contact details at the bottom of this Cookie Policy. If you have a complaint about how we handle your data, we would like to hear from you, but you also have the right to submit a complaint to the supervisory authority (the Information Commissioner's Office (ICO)).9. Enabling/disabling and deleting cookiesYou can use your internet browser to automatically or manually delete cookies. You can also specify that certain cookies may not be placed. Another option is to change the settings of your internet browser so that you receive a message each time a cookie is placed. For more information about these options, please refer to the instructions in the Help section of your browser.Please note that our website may not work properly if all cookies are disabled. If you do delete the cookies in your browser, they will be placed again after your consent when you visit our websites again.10. Contact detailsFor questions and/or comments about our Cookie Policy and this statement, please contact us by using the following contact details:REALTIME
Willows Farm Studios
Ballam Road
Westby
PR4 3PN
United Kingdom
Website: https://www.realtimeuk.com
Email: info@realtimeuk.com
Phone number: +44 (0) 1772 682363This Cookie Policy was synchronised with cookiedatabase.org on 11th May 2020
